- Go. Get the door.
- Here we are.
Go. Push.
- Oh, God.
- Push.
No, no, no. Turn it
around. Really shove it.
You'll break it. Shove
it through. Break it!
You shove it. Shove it back.
Here we go.
Don't break the
branches, Dwight.
All right.
I got a splinter. Well, suck
it up. We all have problems.
Hey, everybody.
Look what we have.
Nice, huh?
I've got it leveraged.
- Push. Straight up.
- On three. Ready?
- Big. One, two, three.
- One, two, three.
Merry Christmas.
Did it work?
Well, sort of.
Why did you get it so big?
A, that's what she said, and,
B, I wanted it to be impressive.
The biggest day of the year
deserves the biggest tree of the year.
But what are we gonna
do with this hacked-off part?
Well, that is a perfectly
good mini-tree, Kevin,
and we are going
to sell that to charity.
That's what
Christmas is all about.
So this year, for the first time
ever, I got Pam in Secret Santa,
and I got her this teapot,
which I know she really wants,
so she can make tea at her desk.
But I'm also gonna stuff
it with some inside jokes.
Like, this is my high
school yearbook photo.
She saw it at the party,
and it really makes her laugh.
Not sure why.
What else?
This is a hot sauce packet.
She put this on a hot
dog a couple years ago
because she thought
it was ketchup.
And it was really funny,
so I kept the other two.
This would take a little too
long to explain, so I won't.
And this is the card.
Because Christmas is the
time to tell people how you feel.
Is there anything we're missing?
Phyllis, you got the lights?
Yes, I got those
cute little ones.
Do you think I should
have gotten the big ones?
We'll see.
Angela drafted me into the
party planning committee.
Her memo said that we need to
prepare for every possible disaster,
which to me seems excessive.
Merry Christmas!
Ho, ho, ho, pimp.
I'm kidding. What do
we got? What do we got?
How many plates
are we getting? Fifty.
Double it. Double everything.
Double ice cream. Double napkins.
Double it. On me.
It was a tough year. I had
to fire somebody this year.
This party has to really rock.
Check it out. Christmas
bonus, 3,000 Gs.
I got this for helping
save the company money.
So I guess some good came
out of firing Devon after all.
Maybe I should call
him and tell him that.
I want people to cut loose. I
want people making out in closets.
I want people hanging from the
ceilings, lamp shades on the heads.
I want it to be a
Playboy Mansion party.
And also, I want you to know and spread the
word that I will have my digital camera.
And I'll be taking
pictures all along the way.
And the best and
craziest thing that happens
will be on the cover of
the newsletter. Incentive.
You do realize that we
can't serve liquor at the party.
Yeah. I know. Damn it.
Stupid corporate wet blankets.
Like booze ever killed anybody.
One. Two. Three.
You guys should
use a hand truck.
Do we have one? No.
Will you help me?
No! No way. It...
No. Come on, Mike.
Let me borrow the hat
for just a couple of hours.
You wanna be Santa? Yeah.
Have you ever seen Santa?
Yeah, I've seen Santa. Okay.
Who cares? Well, I'm
sorry. It just doesn't work.
Michael, I would
like to be the elf.
That makes sense because
he has elfish features.
Okay, everyone. Listen up.
It is time to get your
presents, wrap them
and place them
under the tree, like so.
If you do not get your present
wrapped and under the tree
within the next five minutes,
you will be disqualified
from Secret Santa. All right?
No exceptions except Michael.
I got Angela.
She is into these posters
of babies dressed as adults.
I got her one of those.
I felt kind of
weird buying that.
I got Creed. And to tell you the truth,
I don't know anything about Creed.
I know his name's Creed. I
know he works right over there.
I think he's Irish and I...
I got him this
shamrock keychain.
I got myself for Secret Santa.
I was supposed to tell
somebody, but I didn't.
You get something
good this year?
I think I did a pretty good
job. Yeah? Who did you have?
Well, I can't tell you,
'cause it's a secret.
I think I got something
pretty nice for my guy.
Yeah? I spent a lot of
dough. Lot of dough. Wow.
Well, there's a $20
limit, right? So... Yeah.
I wanted this party to be really special
so I sort of went above and beyond.
That's great. Well, don't tell
me who it is, 'cause I can...
It was Ryan. Yeah. I have Ryan.
Gather round. Secret Santa,
let's go. Let's go. Come on.
Stanley, no. I'm gonna handle
the cord. Okay, safety reasons.
I know how to plug something in.
I want to do it.
All right, let's count it down,
like Rockefeller Center.
Ready?
- Three, two, one.
Not great.
I'm sorry, everybody.
I think the tree looks nice.
Hey, I could get some
flares from my car.
No. No. Shake it off, everybody.
Just, let's do Secret Santa.
Presents are the best way to
show someone how much you care.
It is like this tangible thing
that you can point to and say,
"Hey, man, I love you
this many dollars' worth."
First present, Oscar.
Shower radio. Neat.
Oh, good, that was from me.
Thanks, Kelly. You know
I was gonna get one of...
Okay. Okay. That's enough.
Let's keep it moving on.
Jim. Oh, cool.
That's from me.
Great.
Where did you get it?
I don't know. It
was so long ago.
He obviously forgot
to get me something,
and then he went into his closet
and dug out this little number
and then threw it in a bag.
Yep. That's exactly
what happened.
Pam.
Oh, my God!
Thank you very much,
Santa, whoever you are.
It's awesome. There's
a little more to it.
All right. Next.
Ryan. No. Don't.
Whoa, a video iPod.
Whoa. Wow. Jeez.
Somebody really got carried
away with the spirit of Christmas.
That was me. I got
carried away with the spirit.
Wasn't there a
$20 limit on the gift?
This is 400 bucks.
You don't know that.
Yeah, you left the price tag on.
I did? Yeah.
What? Oh, shoot. Wow.
Okay, well, who cares? It
doesn't matter what I spent.
What matters is that
Christmas is fun, right?
Michael. Oh, hey, for me.
What is in here?
Oh, come on.
I knitted it for you.
An oven mitt?
Okay.
So Phyllis is basically saying,
"Hey, Michael, I know you did
a lot to help the office this year"
"but I only care about you a
homemade oven mitt's worth."
I gave Ryan an iPod.
Should we just keep
opening up the presents?
We don't do anything until
Michael gives us further instructions.
I got it.
We are going to turn
Secret Santa into Yankee Swap.
What is Yankee Swap?
One person chooses a gift.
The next person can either choose
a gift or steal that person's gift.
If your gift gets stolen, then
you can steal someone else's gift
or choose a new gift.
I thought that was
called Nasty Christmas.
Yeah, we call it White Elephant.
Well, I call it fun!
Why are we doing this?
Because it's better.
Because it's more special.
It sounds mean. Shut it.
No, it's not... Okay,
just give it a shot.
Michael should have asked
the party planning committee first.
He's not supposed to just spring
things on us out of nowhere.
Okay, Meredith is up
first. Here's the deal.
You can either pick a new gift
or you can steal
somebody else's gift
that they've already
gotten, like the oven mitt.
I'll take the teapot.
Oh. Shouldn't we...
I bought that specifically
for Pam. Yankee Swap!
That's what makes it fun.
Pam, you can steal the oven
mitt now. I'll take the iPod.
And I have to give it to
her? I don't have a choice?
Yes. Now, you can
steal the oven mitt,
the old shirt or the shower
radio or pick a new gift.
That was meant for
Kelly. Yeah, I figured.
I think this is going great.
Yikes.
Well, it's for Angela, so...
That's, like, the creepiest
thing that I've ever seen.
Angela, you're up.
I'll take the poster.
Some people like these.
I will steal the iPod.
Everyone wants the iPod.
It's a huge hit. It is almost
a Christmas miracle.
Oh, well, Oscar, you little
gourmand, you have the next turn.
I'll take the teapot. Damn it.
Okay. Moving along,
Meredith, let's go.
I really want the iPod.
It's already been stolen this
round. Pick something else.
I hope nobody takes this
baby, 'cause this is great.
Wow, look at that
fine craftsmanship.
Somebody really put a lot
of work into that. It's beautiful.
I'll take the oven mitt.
Sucker!
See, I wanted somebody to take
it. Boom! Reverse psychology.
Reverse psychology
is an awesome tool.
I don't know if you
guys know about it,
but basically you make someone
think the opposite of what you believe
and that tricks them into
doing something stupid.
Works like a charm.
"In addition to these
paint ball pellets,"
"your gift includes two paint
ball lessons with Dwight Shrute."
You and me, Michael. Yes.
Who wants to take paint ball lessons?
How is that better than an iPod?
I never said it was
better than an iPod.
Michael keeps bragging about
his iPod, but you know what?
Two paint ball lessons with
someone as experienced as I am
is worth easily, like, 2 grand.
Take that, Saddam.
Last gift, Kevin.
I want the foot bath.
That's the thing
I bought myself.
I'm really psyched to use it.
Maybe I should
have taken the iPod.
Oh, shoot.
Pam, steal something
or pick the final gift.
- I want the iPod.
- Damn it.
Sure you don't want the teapot?
Well, I mean, it's
an iPod. But... Right.
Sorry, I... No. No.
Definitely. It's...
Okay, well, I guess I will
take that book of short stories.
Yes! There you go. I
want the tea pot. Gracias.
Got to be kidding me.
Yankee Swap is
like Machiavelli meets
Christmas.
What is she so upset about?
Maybe because you
hated her present so much.
Come on! I think that
Yankee Swap was a big hit.
I think it was a success,
and I'm the one who ended up
with Dwight's stupid paint ball pellets.
Yeah, but, Michael, the point is that
we all bought gifts for specific people.
And you should have just bought
a $20 gift like everyone else.
Well, I didn't.
I got a big bonus
because I fired Devon,
and I used the money to buy
something awesome. Sue me!
You got a bonus check?
How much?
It wasn't... It wasn't
that much. It was $3,000.
All right, I'm done now.
Unbelievable.
I do the nicest thing that anyone
has ever done for these people,
and they freak out.
Well, happy birthday, Jesus.
Sorry your party's so lame.
It comes to $166.41.
All right, now, you're the expert. Is
this enough to get 20 people plastered?
Fifteen bottles of vodka?
Yeah, that should do
it. Cool, cool. Box it up.
I bought this teapot for Pam,
and I know she really wants it.
So, can I trade you
for it? No trades.
Come on. It's a shamrock
keychain. Good luck.
"A real man makes his
own luck." Billy Zane, Titanic.
Look it has sentimental value,
Dwight. Can I buy it from you?
No. I want it. I'm
going to use it.
You don't even drink tea. True.
But I get sinus infections, and
sinus infections can be cured
by making your tea from
green tea leaf stems...
Okay. And pouring it directly
into your nose, like so.
To think that my gift to
Pam will be used for that,
it's a little too
much to handle.
This is awesome.
I know. It's totally gonna
change the way I work out.
Yeah, I was gonna get you one of
these for Christmas, now I don't have to.
I'm gonna save a ton of money.
So what are you
gonna get me instead?
I don't know. Probably,
like, a sweater or something.
Uh-oh.
Looks like Santa
was a little naughty.
What is that?
This is Christmas
spirit, as in spirits, booze.
We can drink?
We're really not
supposed to serve alcohol.
Zip it, Toby! Just... I
mean, it's a party. Come on.
If I can't throw a good party for my
employees, then I am a terrible boss.
Who wants a drink? Me. Please.
Go! Here we go!
The deal is that
this is my last hurrah,
'cause I made a
New Year's resolution
that I'm not gonna drink
anymore during the week.
- Hi, guys.
- Hey.
Does everyone know
my boyfriend, Bob Vance?
Kevin Malone. Bob
Vance, Vance Refrigeration.
Stanley Hudson. Bob
Ryan Howard. Bob
Vance, Vance Refrigeration.
What line of work you in, Bob?
I think after I lost Culpepper
and T.O. it was over, man.
Oh, yeah, I need McMahon,
Deion Branch to have big
games, or else I'm done.
It's possible.
I can't believe you traded
Shaun Alexander, man.
I had to, I needed defense.
Come on! Shaun Alexander?
He's the best back in the league.
- It's defense.
Oh, no. That's not worth it.
- It is worth it.
Never. DARRYL: Are
you kidding? You wait.
Anybody making out in
here? Not yet. Give it time.
Oh, hey, Ebenezer, boink.
Okay, how's it going in here?
We're running low on cups. Do you
want me to just run out and get some?
Yeah, there should
be some... No, no, no.
We'll find some.
Don't leave the party.
One, two, three!
Kudos to Ryan, king
of the party committee.
- Oh, no.
- Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I really did not do anything.
Oh, no, no. No false
modesty, my friend.
You know, you don't have
to answer calls during a party.
Just thought you should know.
No, I was just checking
out my present.
But... I traded with Dwight.
Just, I figured, you know,
you went to a lot of
trouble and it means a lot.
And also, Roy got me an iPod
or was going to
get me an iPod, so...
Well, either way.
This is an amazing gift
because it comes with bonus gifts.
Look inside.
Oh, my God! The
yearbook picture.
Yeah, I think I made
the right choice.
Oh, my God! It's incredible.
Is this the bottle timer?
I didn't think you were gonna
get that one. I really didn't.
This is so awesome.
Not bad. And if it couldn't go to Ryan,
you are the guy I'd want it to go to.
Thank you. You're welcome.
Merry Christmas,
asswipe. No way.
Oh, you're kidding me. Packer!
Yes! Todd Packer,
ladies and gentlemen.
What's up, my
nerds? Check it out!
Oh, no, no. Oh, look at
that. Icing on the cake.
Pacman need a drinky.
Oh, let's fix you up.
Who wants to fix up... Toby?
Toby's gonna fix you up.
Yeah.
Darryl. There you go.
You earned it.
That's okay, Mike.
No, no, no, no. I really,
really want you to have it.
All right. Thanks, man.
Hey, Merry Christmas.
Whose butt is that? Mine.
Oh, how did I not guess that?
Lampshade on
head! It's happening!
Oh, no.
Hey. Oh, hello there.
But what are you
doing? I don't know.
You shouldn't do things like that.
The man is supposed to do that.
- Thanks for the party, Michael.
- Yeah.
Oh, hey... Listen up. We're
going to Poor Richard's.
Who's in? I'm in.
Yes.
Michael? Poor Richard's?
Yeah. That sounds good.
Christmas is awesome.
First of all, you get to spend
time with people you love.
Secondly, you can get drunk
and no one can say anything.
Third, you give presents. What's
better than giving presents?
And fourth, getting presents. So,
four things. Not bad for one day.
It's really the greatest
day of all time.
Hey, Meredith.
Heading over to
Poor Richard's? Yep.
Cool, cool, cool.
Do you need a ride?
All right, let's head out.
Sounds good. Do
you have a coat? Yeah.
Okay!